Temitope Joseph Orubuloye

(+234) 90781237851, (+234) 07025715756 · Temitopeorubuloye3@gmail.com Church road kabala doki, Kaduna, Nigeria

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Knowledgeable Computer Operator, effective at setting controls and running specific daily tasks.

Collaborative and communicative with proven history of quickly fixing minor issues and helping resolve more advanced problems. Meticulous in data management procedures. Dependable Computer Operator specializes in accepting, transmitting and storing sensitive customer data. Maintains strict adherence to applicable regulatory and legal requirements to mitigate risk and liability.

KEY COMPETENCIES

Customer Service WordPress Development Graphic Design File Transfer Critical thinking skills Blogging

Website Development Digital Marketing Website Modification

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Aprime Tech Agency

Blogger / SEO content Writer

November 2022 - Till date

Worked as a Frontend/WordPress website Developer, Graphic Designer and a Digital Marketer

Emperior Concepts

November 2021 - November 2023

Blogger / SEO content Writer

Worked as a blogger and a search engine optimization(SEO) content writer

Fina white House Hotels

February 2020 - November 2022

Receptionist Receptionist

Worked with Excel and registration of clients as a front desk attendant (Receptionist)

Khemsafe Computer Institute

April 2017 - September 2017

Tech student

Studied Basics of website development, graphic designs, as a student

Bindave Machine/computer operator

March 2013 - September 2016

Prepared and served a variety of beverages with precision and creativity, consistently meeting or exceeding quality standards, and receiving compliments for latte art and presentation.

EDUCATION & CERTIFICATIONS

Federal Polytechnic kaura Namoda

Higher National Diploma Computer Science

Federal Polytechnic kaura Namoda

Ordinary National Diploma Computer Science

Louisana De prince

Secondary

St. Michaels / First African

NurseryPrimary

EXTRACURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

Aprime Tech Agency

Web developer, Graphic Designer and Digital Marketer

Emperor Concepts

Blogger / SEO content Writer